Inventory of the Francis E. Warren Papers, 1867-1974
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- Series III. Warren Live Stock Company, 1882-1957
  - Subseries 2. Federal Government, 1891-1918; 1.6 cubic ft. (4 document boxes)
    - Subsubseries 2. Fencing Cases, 1905-1912
      - Fencing Cases, 1907-1912; microfilm reel 204 (Box 105, Folder 2)
      - Fencing Cases, 1905; microfilm reel 204 (Box 105, Folder 3)
      - Fencing Cases, 1906; microfilm reel 204 (Box 105, Folder 4)
      - Fencing Cases, 1906; microfilm reel 204 (Box 105, Folder 5)
      - Fencing Cases, 1906; microfilm reel 204 (Box 105, Folder 6)
      - Fencing Cases, 1906; microfilm reel 204 (Box 105, Folder 7)
      - Fencing Cases, 1907-1911; microfilm reel 204 (Box 105, Folder 8)
      - Fencing Cases, 1906; microfilm reel 204 (Box 105, Folder 9)
      - Fencing Cases, n.d.; microfilm reel 204 (Box 105, Folder 10)
      - Fencing Cases, 1910,n.d.; microfilm reel 204 (Box 105, Folder 11)
      - Fencing Cases, n.d.; microfilm reel 204 (Box 105, Folder 12)
      - Fencing Case, n.d.; microfilm reel 204 (Box 105, Folder 13)
      - Fencing Cases, 1906; microfilm reel 204 (Box 105, Folder 14)
      - Fencing Cases, 1906; microfilm reel 205 (Box 106, Folder 1-6)
      - Fencing Cases, 1906-1907; microfilm reel 205 (Box 106, Folder 7-8)
      - Fencing Cases, n.d.; microfilm reel 205 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Suberies III. Land and Grazing Leases, Statements, Bills of Sale, and Mortgages, 1884-1957; 3.0 cubic ft. (8 document boxes)
    Arranged chronologically by year and alphabetically by company, agency, or personal name of the Signer. Contains grazing leases, Union Pacific land leases, bills of sale, mortgages, agreements, statements, school and state land leases and reservoir filings all pertaining to Warren Live Stock Company.
    - Grazing Leases, 1903-1909; microfilm reel 206 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Grazing Leases, 1910-1914; microfilm reel 206 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - U.P. Land Leases, 1910-1918; microfilm reel 206 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Land Leases, 1910-1911; statements, bills of sale, mortgages; microfilm reel 206 (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Land Leases, 1912; agreements; microfilm reel 206 (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Land Leases, 1913; agreements; microfilm reel 206 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Land Leases, 1914-1915; agreements; microfilm reel 206 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Land Leases, 1916-1917; agreements; microfilm reel 206 (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Land Leases, 1884-1890; statements, bills of sale, mortgages; microfilm reel 206 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Land Leases, 1891-1895; statements, bills of sale, mortgages; microfilm reel 206 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Land Leases, 1896-1899; statements, bills of sale, mortgages; microfilm reel 206 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Land Leases, 1900-1901; statements, bills of sale, mortgages; microfilm reel 206 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Land Leases, 1902; statements, bills of sale, mortgages; microfilm reel 206 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Land Leases, 1903; statements, bills of sale, mortgages; microfilm reel 206 (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Land Leases, 1904; statements, bills of sale, mortgages; microfilm reel 206 (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Land Leases, 1905; statements, bills of sale, mortgages; microfilm reel 206 (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Land Leases, 1906; statements, bills of sale, mortgages; microfilm reel 206 (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - Land Leases, 1907-1908; statements, bills of sale, mortgages; microfilm reel 206 (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - Land Leases, 1909; statements, bills of sale, mortgages; microfilm reel 206 (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - Land Leases, 1912; statements, bills of sale, mortgages; microfilm reel 206 (Box 108, Folder 12)
    - Land Leases, statements, bills of sale, mortgages; microfilm reel 206 (Box 108, Folder 13)
    - State Land Leases, 1905-1907; microfilm reel 207 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - State Land Leases, 1908-1910; microfilm reel 207 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - State Land Leases, 1911-1913; microfilm reel 207 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Land Lease Applications, 1908-1916; microfilm reel 207 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - State Land Leases, 1888-1891; microfilm reel 207 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - State Land Leases, 1892-1893; microfilm reel 207 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - State Land Leases, 1895-1896; microfilm reel 207 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - State Land Leases, 1897-1898; microfilm reel 207 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - State Land Leases, 1899-1900; microfilm reel 207 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - State Land Leases, 1901; microfilm reel 207 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - State Land Leases, 1902; microfilm reel 207 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - State Land Leases, 1903-1904; microfilm reel 207 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Employee Statements:
    - A-B, 1900-1901,n.d.; microfilm reel 207 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - C-D, 1900-1901,n.d.; microfilm reel 207 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - E-F, 1900-1901,n.d.; microfilm reel 207 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - G-H, 1900-1901,n.d.; microfilm reel 207 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - I-J, 1900-1901,n.d.; microfilm reel 207 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - K-L, 1900-1901,n.d.; microfilm reel 207 (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - M-N, 1900-1901,n.d.; microfilm reel 207 (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - O-P, 1900-1901,n.d.; microfilm reel 207 (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Q-R, 1900-1901,n.d.; microfilm reel 207 (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - S-T, 1900-1901,n.d.; microfilm reel 207 (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - U-V, 1901,n.d.; microfilm reel 207 (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - W-Z, 1900-1901,n.d.; microfilm reel 207 (Box 111, Folder 12)
    - Profit-Loss Statement, 1884-1929; microfilm reel 207 (Box 111, Folder 13)
    - Legal and Financial Papers, 1884-1916; services and supplies, bills of sale for livestock and merchandise; microfilm reel 208 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Legal and Financial Papers, 1908-1915,n.d.; general records of land holdings, owned by others or owners unknown; microfilm reel 208 (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Legal and Financial Papers, 1902-1908,n.d.; land, inventory, and tax receipts; microfilm reel 208 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Legal and Financial Papers, 1897-1915; records regarding acquisitions of state and federal lands; microfilm reel 208 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Legal and Financial Papers, 1883-1915; transactions, chattel mortgages, bonds, land; microfilm reel 208 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Legal and Financial Papers, 1883-1915; transactions, chattel mortgages, bonds, land; microfilm reel 208 (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Legal and Financial Papers, 1889; list of brands owned by Warren Live Stock; microfilm reel 208 (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - Legal and Financial Papers, 1956-1957; Pershing stock purchases; microfilm reel 208 (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - Legal and Financial Papers, 1957; Pershing transaction; microfilm reel 208 (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - Land Leases, 1884-1889; microfilm reel 208 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Land Leases, 1891-1895; microfilm reel 208 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Land Leases, 1896-1899; microfilm reel 208 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Land Leases, 1900-1901; microfilm reel 208 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Land Leases, Statements, 1902-1904; microfilm reel 208 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Reservoir Filings, 1908; microfilm reel 208 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Land Leases, 1894; microfilm reel 208 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 4. Ledgers, 1884-1936; 4.07 cubic ft. (5 record storage cartons)
    Arranged chronologically by year and by company or personal name. Contains records of daily transactions between Warren Live Stock and various customers. Includes bills payable and bills receivable.
    - Ledger, 1883-1886; microfilm reel 209 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Ledger, 1886-1889; microfilm reel 209 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Ledger, 1889-1901; microfilm reel 209 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Ledger, 1889-1891; microfilm reel 209 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Ledger, 1892-1895; microfilm reel 210 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Ledger, 1894-1895; microfilm reel 210 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Ledger, 1896-1899; microfilm reel 210 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Ledger, 1899-1911; microfilm reel 210 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Ledger, 1899-1903; microfilm reel 211 (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Ledger, 1903-1906; microfilm reel 211 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Ledger, 1906-1908; microfilm reel 212 (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Ledger, 1908-1909; microfilm reel 212 (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Ledger, 1910-1911; microfilm reel 213 (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Ledger, 1930-1936; microfilm reel 213 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Employee Ledger, 1897-1899; microfilm reel 213 (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Employee Ledger, 1911-1912; microfilm reel 214 (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Balance Sheets, 1896-1908; microfilm reel 214 (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Balance Sheets, 1908-1911; microfilm reel 215 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 5. Journals, 1883-1953; 10.13 cubic ft. (11 record storage cartons)
    Arranged chronologically by year. Contains cash on hand statements for Warren Live Stock and other companies affiliated with them.
    - August 12, 1883-July 1884, microfilm reel 216 (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - November 1, 1883-July 31, 1886, microfilm reel 216 (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - May 1, 1885-January 31, 1889, microfilm reel 216 (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - August 1, 1886-June 30 1889, microfilm reel 216 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - August 1, 1887-February 1, 1889, microfilm reel 217 (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - June 19, 1889-December 31, 1890, microfilm reel 217 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - July 1, 1889-December 31, 1891, microfilm reel 217 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - February 1, 1889-May 26, 1890, microfilm reel 218 (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - January 2, 1893-July 31, 1901, microfilm reel 218 (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - August 6, 1894-December 31, 1895, microfilm reel 218 (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - January 2, 1892-December 31, 1895, microfilm reel 219 (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - January 1, 1896-May 31, 1899, microfilm reel 219 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - June 1, 1899-October 31, 1901, microfilm reel 220 (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - November 1, 1901-April 30, 1904, microfilm reel 220 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - May 2, 1904-September 29, 1906, microfilm reel 221 (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - October 1, 1906-September 30, 1908, microfilm reel 221 (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - March 1, 1908-December 31, 1912, microfilm reel 221 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - October 1, 1908-April 30, 1910, microfilm reel 222 (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - May 2, 1910-September 30, 1911, microfilm reel 222 (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - October 2, 1911-April 30, 1913, microfilm reel 222 (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - January 1, 1913-December 30, 1919, microfilm reel 223 (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - May 1, 1913-October 31, 1914, microfilm reel 223 (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - November 2, 1914-April 24, 1916, microfilm reel 223 (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - April 24, 1916-August 2, 1917, microfilm reel 224 (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - August 2, 1917-December 31, 1918, microfilm reel 224 (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - December 31, 1918-May 27, 1920, microfilm reel 224 (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - May 27, 1920-March 18, 1922, microfilm reel 225 (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - March 18, 1922, October 15, 1923, microfilm reel 225 (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - October 16, 1923-June 9, 1925, microfilm reel 225 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - June 9, 1925-December 31, 1926, microfilm reel 226 (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - January 3, 1927-August 2, 1928, microfilm reel 226 (Box 162, Folder 1)
    - August 2, 1928-April 2, 1930, microfilm reel 226 (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - April 2, 1930-December 31, 1931, microfilm reel 227 (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - January 2, 1932-December 27, 1933, microfilm reel 227 (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - December 28, 1933-December 9, 1935, microfilm reel 227 (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - December 9, 1935-September 21, 1937, microfilm reel 228 (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - September 22, 1937-July 25, 1939, microfilm reel 228 (Box 168, Folder 1)
    - July 25, 1939-June 16, 1941, microfilm reel 228 (Box 169, Folder 1)
    - June 17, 1941-May 10, 1943, microfilm reel 229 (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - May 11, 1943-June 25, 1945, microfilm reel 229 (Box 171, Folder 1)
    - June 26, 1945-July 7, 1947, microfilm reel 229 (Box 172, Folder 1)
    - July 7, 1947-June 30, 1949, microfilm reel 230 (Box 173, Folder 1)
    - June 30, 1949-June 2, 1951, microfilm reel 230 (Box 174, Folder 1)
    - June 21, 1951-June 1, 1953, microfilm reel 230 (Box 175, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 6. General Correspondence and Records, 1883-1949; 8.13 cubic ft. (9 record storage cartons)
    Arranged chronologically by year. Letterpress copybooks containing outgoing correspondence from Warren Live Stock to various companies and individuals with which it did business.
    - Bound Receipts, 1883-1885; microfilm reel 231 (Box 176, Folder 1)
    - Letterpress Copybooks:
    - July 20, 1886-February 21, 1889, microfilm reel 232 (Box 177, Folder 1)
    - October 23, 1886-August 22, 1887, microfilm reel 232 (Box 177, Folder 2)
    - August 22, 1887-April 14, 1888, microfilm reel 233 (Box 177, Folder 3)
    - April 14, 1888-December 13, 1888, microfilm reel 233 (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - December 13, 1888-July 26, 1889, microfilm reel 234 (Box 177, Folder 5)
    - July 26, 1889-April 5, 1890, microfilm reel 234 (Box 177, Folder 6)
    - April 5, 1890-October 25, 1890, microfilm reel 235 (Box 177, Folder 7)
    - October 25, 1890-April 19, 1891, microfilm reel 235 (Box 177, Folder 8)
    - April 20, 1891-September 18, 1891, microfilm reel 236 (Box 177, Folder 9)
    - September 18, 1891-February 5, 1892, microfilm reel 236 (Box 178, Folder 1)
    - February 5, 1892-June 21, 1892, microfilm reel 236 (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - June 22, 1892-December 21, 1892, microfilm reel 237 (Box 178, Folder 3)
    - January 10, 1893-June 12, 1893, microfilm reel 237 (Box 178, Folder 4)
    - June 12, 1893-July 8, 1893, microfilm reel 238 (Box 178, Folder 5)
    - November 1, 1893 April 28, 1894, microfilm reel 238 (Box 178, Folder 6)
    - April 29, 1894-May 29, 1895, microfilm reel 239 (Box 178, Folder 7)
    - May 29, 1895-August 10, 1896, microfilm reel 240 (Box 178, Folder 8)
    - August 10, 1896-October 30, 1897, microfilm reel 241 (Box 179, Folder 1)
    - November 11, 1897-June 15, 1898, microfilm reel 241 (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - June 16, 1898-October 19, 1898, microfilm reel 242 (Box 179, Folder 3)
    - July 8, 1899-December 30, 1899, microfilm reel 243 (Box 179, Folder 4)
    - December 29, 1899-March 21, 1901, microfilm reel 243 (Box 179, Folder 5)
    - March 20, 1901-October 25, 1901, microfilm reel 244 (Box 179, Folder 6)
    - October 28, 1901-September 23, 1902, microfilm reel 244 (Box 179, Folder 7)
    - September 24, 1902-October 30, 1903, microfilm reel 245 (Box 180, Folder 1)
    - October 31, 1903-May 1, 1905, microfilm reel 246 (Box 180, Folder 2)
    - May 1, 1905-January 16, 1907, microfilm reel 247 (Box 180, Folder 3)
    - January 17, 1907-May 29, 1908, microfilm reel 248 (Box 180, Folder 4)
    - May 29, 1908-August 16, 1909, microfilm reel 249 (Box 180, Folder 5)
    - August 17, 1909-December 2, 1910, microfilm reel 250 (Box 180, Folder 6)
    - December 3, 1910-November 4, 1911, microfilm reel 251 (Box 181, Folder 1)
    - November 3, 1911-October 28, 1912, microfilm reel 252 (Box 181, Folder 2)
    - October 28, 1912-January 26, 1914, microfilm reel 253 (Box 181, Folder 3)
    - August 11, 1911-July 3, 1916, microfilm reel 254 (Box 181, Folder 4)
    - January 28, 1914-March 26, 1915, microfilm reel 254 (Box 181, Folder 5)
    - March 26, 1915-July 11, 1916, microfilm reel 255 (Box 182, Folder 1)
    - December 17, 1917-May 31, 1919, microfilm reel 256 (Box 182, Folder 2)
    - June 5, 1919-November 13, 1920, microfilm reel 256 (Box 182, Folder 3)
    - April 1, 1921-February 27, 1923, microfilm reel 258 (Box 182, Folder 4)
    - February 28, 1923-October 22, 1924, microfilm reel 259 (Box 182, Folder 5)
    - Warren Live Stock Records, April 10, 1923-July 1931; microfilm reel 260 (Box 183, Folder 1)
    - October 23, 1924-October 14, 1926, microfilm reel 261 (Box 183, Folder 2)
    - October 16, 1926-December 22, 1928, microfilm reel 262 (Box 183, Folder 3)
    - May 29, 1931-June 25, 1934, microfilm reel 263 (Box 183, Folder 4)
    - June 25, 1934-August 23, 1938, microfilm reel 264 (Box 183, Folder 5)
    - Warren Live Stock Records, December 31, 1929-June 6, 1942; microfilm reel 265 (Box 184, Folder 1)
    - June 15, 1937-December 26, 1939, microfilm reel 266 (Box 184, Folder 2)
    - December 26, 1939-January 22, 1942, microfilm reel 267 (Box 184, Folder 3)
    - January 22, 1942-August 20, 1945, microfilm reel 268 (Box 184, Folder 4)
    - Time Sheets, 1946-1949; microfilm reel 269 (Box 184, Folder 5)
    - August 24, 1945-June 30, 1949, microfilm reel 269 (Box 184, Folder 6)
    - Balance Sheets, June 10, 1942-August 13, 1949; microfilm reel 270 (Box 185, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 7. Financial Record Books, 1879-1939; 1 cubic ft. (1 record storage carton)
    Includes a Warren Live Stock charge blotter, time sheets, (1917-1923, 1931-1939), general ledger index, plat book, lease record (1901 to 1912), land office plats and map of Warren Live Stock lands, trial balance book (1926-1930), and a workers' time book (1899-1904)
    - Warren Live Stock Charge Blotter, 1884-1891; microfilm reel 271 (Box 186, Folder 1)
    - Warren Live Stock Time Sheets, Bills of Loding, Trial Balance, November 1917-March 1923; microfilm reel 271 (Box 186, Folder 2)
    - Warren Live Stock Time Sheets, August 1931-February 1939; microfilm reel 271 (Box 186, Folder 3)
    - Index to General Ledger for Warren Live Stock Co., microfilm reel 271 (Box 186, Folder 4)
    - Plat Book, 1879-1922; microfilm reel 271 (Box 187, Folder 1)
    - Lease Record, 1900-1925; microfilm reel 272 (Box 188, Folder 1)
    - Land Office Plats and Map of Warren Live Stock Company's Lands, 1887-1909; microfilm reel 272 (Box 189, Folder 1)
    - Trial Balance Book, July 21, 1926-May 7, 1930; microfilm reel 273 (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - Workers Time Book, May 1899-July 1904; microfilm reel 273 (Box 190, Folder 2)
    - President's Office, National Wool Growers Association, January 31, 1903-December 3, 1907; microfilm reel 273 (Box 190, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 8. W. W. Gleason Papers, 1901-1911; .25 cubic ft. (1 document box).
    Arranged alphabetically by company or name of addressor. Contains personal and business correspondence received by W.W. Gleason concerning the operation of Warren Live Stock Company and Gleason Mercantile Company. This correspondence includes letters and telegrams from F.E. Warren.
    - A, 1909-1911; microfilm reel 274 (Box 191, Folder 1)
    - B, 1908-1910; microfilm reel 274 (Box 191, Folder 2)
    - C, 1905-1911; microfilm reel 274 (Box 191, Folder 3)
    - D, 1909-1911; microfilm reel 274 (Box 191, Folder 4)
    - E, 1908-1910; microfilm reel 274 (Box 191, Folder 5)
    - F, 1911; microfilm reel 274 (Box 191, Folder 6)
    - G, 1908-1910; microfilm reel 274 (Box 191, Folder 7)
    - H, 1908-1911; microfilm reel 274 (Box 191, Folder 8)
    - I, 1907-1911; microfilm reel 274 (Box 191, Folder 9)
    - K, 1908-1909; microfilm reel 274 (Box 191, Folder 10)
    - L, 1908-1911; microfilm reel 274 (Box 191, Folder 11)
    - M, 1908; microfilm reel 274 (Box 191, Folder 12)
    - N, 1908-1910; microfilm reel 274 (Box 191, Folder 13)
    - O, 1911; microfilm reel 274 (Box 191, Folder 14)
    - P, 1908-1911; microfilm reel 274 (Box 191, Folder 15)
    - R, 1908-1910; microfilm reel 274 (Box 191, Folder 16)
    - S, 1908-1911; microfilm reel 274 (Box 191, Folder 17)
    - T, 1908-1909; microfilm reel 274 (Box 191, Folder 18)
    - U-V, 1908-1910; microfilm reel 274 (Box 191, Folder 19)
    - W, 1907-1911; microfilm reel 274 (Box 191, Folder 20)
    - X-Z, 1909-1910; microfilm reel 274 (Box 191, Folder 21)
- Series IV. Early Business Ventures, 1878-1961; 7.6 cubic ft. (21 document boxes) arranged chronologically.
  Correspondence, legal documents, journals, ledgers, cash books, day books, inventories, and newspaper clippings
  - Subseries 1. Guiterman and Warren, 1878-1880
    - Legal Documents and Correspondence, 1878-1879; microfilm reel 275 (Box 192, Folder 1)
    - Journal, 1878-1879; microfilm reel 275 (Box 192, Folder 2)
    - Day Book, 1878-1880; contains partnership agreement; microfilm reel 275 (Box 192, Folder 3)
    - Ledger, 1878-1880; microfilm reel 275 (Box 192, Folder 4)
    - Employees Ledger, 1879-1880; microfilm reel 275 (Box 192, Folder 5)
    - Invoice Book, 1878-1880; microfilm reel 275 (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 2. Miner and Warren, 1878-1883
    - Legal Documents and Correspondence, 1875-1883; microfilm reel 276 (Box 194, Folder 1)
    - Journal, 1878-1882; contains partnership agreement, inventory and listing of original Miner and Warren holdings; microfilm reel 267 (Box 194, Folder 2)
    - Miner and Warren Wool Journals, 1879-1882; microfilm reel 276 (Box 194, Folder 3)
    - Invoice Book, 1878-1883; bills, receipts, memoranda; microfilm reel 276 (Box 194, Folder 4)
    - Ledger, 1878-1883; microfilm reel 276 (Box 195, Folder 1)
    - Journal, 1882-1883; microfilm reel 276 (Box 195, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 3. Post and Warren, 1880-1884
    - Post and Warren Blotter, 1880-1881; microfilm reel 277 (Box 196, Folder 1)
    - Post and Warren Journal, 1880-1884; microfilm reel 277 (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - Post and Warren Letterbook, 1881-1883; microfilm reel 277 (Box 196, Folder 3)
    - Post and Warren Ledger, ca. 1882; microfilm reel 277 (Box 196, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 4. Brush Swan Electric Light Company, Cheyenne City Gas Company, and Cheyenne Light, Fuel and Power, 1882-1924
    - Articles of Incorporation, 1882; correspondence and receipts; microfilm reel 277 (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - Clippings, 1882-1899; microfilm reel 277 (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - Legal Documents-Brush Swan Electric Light Company, 1882-1905; microfilm reel 277 (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Memos and Receipts, 1883; microfilm reel 277 (Box 197, Folder 4)
    - Legal Documents for Cheyenne City Gas Company, 1883-1884; microfilm reel 277 (Box 197, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1884; microfilm reel 277 (Box 197, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Memos, Notices, 1885; microfilm reel 277 (Box 197, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Receipts, Prospectuses, 1886-1902; microfilm reel 277 (Box 197, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Documents, n.d.; microfilm reel 277 (Box 197, Folder 9)
    - Legal Documents Cheyenne Light Fuel and Power, 1900-1919; microfilm reel 277 (Box 197, Folder 10)
    - Letterbook, 1882-1885; microfilm reel 278 (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - Minute Book, 1882-1903; contains articles of incorporation and by-laws, meeting minutes; microfilm reel 278 (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - Trial Balance Book, 1899-1924; microfilm reel 278 (Box 198, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 5. Cheyenne, Black Hills and Montana Railway Company, 1883-1889
    - Record Book, 1883-1888; contains articles of incorporation, notes, contracts, minutes; microfilm reel 278 (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Legal Documents, 1883; microfilm reel 278 (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - Documents for Dissolution of Cheyenne, Black Hills, Montana Railway Company, 1885-1889; microfilm reel 278 (Box 199, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 6. Cheyenne Carriage Company, 1882-1900
    - Legal Documents, 1882-1900; microfilm reel 278 (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - Pocket Notebook Listing Shareholders, 1883; microfilm reel 278 (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Record Book, 1883-1900; microfilm reel 278 (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Documents, 1893-1900; microfilm reel 278 (Box 200, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 7. Cheyenne Street Railroad Company, 1887-1907
    - Legal Documents, 1888-1893; microfilm reel 278 (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - Record Book, 1887-1903; microfilm reel 278 (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - Public Notice #61, Assignment of Judgment, 1889,1907; microfilm reel 278 (Box 201, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 8. Wyoming Phonograph Company, 1889-1900